epicor.com 2019-05-06

# Privacy Policy | Security Information | Epicor

Epicor Software Corporation along with, as applicable, its parent corporation, as well as any and all subsidiaries, affiliates, successors, and assigns ("Epicor") provides this Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy") to help you understand how we collect, use and disclose information, including personal information that you may provide to us or that we may obtain as you use and access our Site. We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, so please check back here periodically. This Privacy Policy applies to www.epicor.com (the “Site”) This Privacy Policy explains Epicor's information practices including:

  * How Epicor uses the personal information you share with us and that we learn about you because of our relationship when you use the Site.
  * What personal information, if any, Epicor may share about you and the conditions we use to protect your information if it must be shared that has been collected through the Site.
  * Other things you should know about privacy and Epicor.

"Personal Information" includes information that alone or when in combination with other information may be used to readily identify, contact, or locate you or a specific individual.

For information regarding Epicor’s privacy policy respecting its human capital management (HCM) solution see HCM Solution Privacy Policy.

## Collected Information and Usage

By using the Site, you consent to the collection and use of your Personal Information by Epicor consistent with applicable data protection law and this Privacy Policy which is expressly incorporated into the Terms. Epicor collects and uses the information you provide to us, including information obtained from your use of this Site. We may use or share Personal Information (e.g., name, address, telephone number, email address, and location) where it is necessary for us to complete a transaction or do something that you have asked us to do. Also, we may use the information that we collect for our business purposes to develop, enhance, and improve our products and services, and for advertising and marketing consistent with this Privacy Policy. By using the Site, you acknowledge, consent and agree that Epicor may collect, process, and use the information that you provide to us and that such information shall only be used by Epicor or third parties acting under Epicor’s direction in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Epicor collects and uses information from you in several ways:

**The Epicor Site.**  Epicor (or Epicor vendors and suppliers) may observe your activities, preferences, and transactional data (such as your IP address and browser type) as well as related usage behavior depending on whether you are using our Site or a particular Epicor Product. We may use this data for any purpose unless we tell you otherwise in connection with a particular Site or product. While we may collect or log this information, we do not identify you or match this non-Personal Information with your other Personal Information unless or except if we believe doing so will help us better respond to a request you have made or otherwise personalize your experience in using the Site. Where such non-Personal Information is linked to your Personal Information we will treat such information as Personal Information.

**Use of Cookies.**  The Epicor Site uses "cookies" and related technologies to help you personalize your online experience and in our electronic communications with you. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies and related technologies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Epicor pages, or register with Epicor sites or services, a cookie helps Epicor to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information and return user log in. When you return to the Site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Site you visit.

**E-Commerce.**  You may be asked to share Personal Information such as your name, address, telephone number, and email address when you make purchases, seek customer or technical support or otherwise interact with Epicor, including on-line. When you buy direct from Epicor, these purchase transactions may be conducted through Epicor vendors and suppliers. Vendors and suppliers engaged by Epicor on behalf of Epicor may have their use of your Personal Information limited by this Privacy Policy, contractual restrictions, and applicable law. Epicor (through its vendors or suppliers) may limit the acceptance of orders to particular jurisdictions and as permitted by applicable law. You may also make purchases of Epicor Products; seek customer or technical support through Epicor's distributors or service providers. In these circumstances, the collection of your Personal Information may occur directly by the distributor or service provider or a third-party partner on their web site, which will state the privacy policy or policies governing the collection of such information.

**Product Registration & Technical Support.** Epicor may allow its customers to register products online or through similar ways. Personal Information or data provided for such purposes may be used to carry out the request, service, or agreement for which the information is submitted. With your consent and as otherwise permitted by law, we may also use the information you provide in online registration forms to notify you periodically about important changes to the Site or Application (such as a change to this Privacy Policy or notice of a security breach), new Epicor products and services, and special offers and promotions that may be of interest to you. If you register, we may ask for, among other things, your name, address, email, telephone number, type of product purchased, or other product-identifying information.

**Online Promotions, Contests and Sweepstakes.**  You may be asked to provide an email address or screen name, or other Personal Information, for entry into a particular promotion, including sweepstakes and contests, so that we can let you know if you won a prize. The specific rules and regulations governing the particular promotion, contest or sweepstakes will vary and your participation constitutes your agreement to abide by those rules and regulations. Certain promotions, contests or sweepstakes may be run by an Epicor service provider or vendor or co-branded with one of our partners. In these instances, the collection of your Personal Information may occur directly by the service provider or vendor or a third-party partner on their Site. The promotion will state the privacy policy or policies governing the collection of such information if they should differ from this Privacy Policy.

**Children.**  The Epicor Site and Epicor’s products are not directed at children. If you are under 18 or otherwise would be required to have parent or guardian consent to share information with Epicor, you should not send any information about yourself to us. As required by law, if a person under 13 submits information through any part of an Epicor Site or an Epicor Product, and we learn the person submitting the information is such a child, we will attempt to delete this information as soon as possible.

**When Epicor May Share Collected Information.**  As previously mentioned in this Privacy Policy, Epicor may share Personal Information within Epicor (including our worldwide affiliates and other members of the Epicor Group) to fulfill its obligations to you and operate its business consistent with this Privacy Policy and applicable data protection law. In addition to what is expressly stated in this Privacy Policy, we may also share your Personal Information with third parties in the following situations:

**Epicor Subsidiaries, Affiliates, Vendors and Suppliers.**  Epicor works with many affiliated third parties, vendors, distributors, and suppliers. To the extent it is necessary for these groups to provide their products and services to us and provide products and services you have requested, these third parties may have access to or process your Personal Information. Epicor may also sometimes permit our authorized service providers to have access to aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related Site or Application information. These transfers of aggregate statistics do not involve Personal Information or data.

**Recruitment and Job Applications.**  Residents of the United States may provide us with Personal Information through our Site. Personal information such as that contained on a resume or curriculum vitae may be submitted in connection with a job application or inquiry. We may use this information throughout Epicor (worldwide) for the purpose of employment consideration or your inquiry. We may keep your information on file for future consideration. When you submit such information you consent to worldwide processing of this information.

**Enabling Services.**  Epicor offers a variety of services and functions through its Sites ("Epicor Services"). Personal Information that is collected through a Site may be used and/or disclosed to third parties in order to enable us to provide Epicor Services. For example, the Epicor Site may allow you to interface with a third party Site or application. To facilitate that connection, we may use your Personal Information and/or disclose your Personal Information to third parties.

**Public Areas.**  Any information disclosed in public areas of an Epicor Site or to the extent possible in an Epicor Product or other Site (Facebook, YouTube, Twitter, etc.) will become public information. We cannot control the use of information disclosed in public forums, such as forums, bulletin boards, blogs, chat rooms, and networking functions of mobile-device applications. You should exercise caution when disclosing information in these public areas, and be careful how you disclose your Personal Information. Content posted in public areas of the Epicor Site or Epicor Products, including advice and opinions, represent the views and is the responsibility of those who post the content. Epicor does not necessarily endorse, support, verify, or agree with the content posted.

**Mergers and Acquisitions.**  If Epicor should ever merge with another company, or if Epicor should decide to buy, sell, or reorganize some part or all of its business, Epicor may be required to transfer your Personal Information and in such events your Personal Information may be used or transferred in accordance with this Privacy Policy and as permitted by law.

**As Required by Law and Other Extraordinary Disclosures.**  Epicor may be required to disclose your Personal Information if it: (i) believes in its sole judgment that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process (such as a court order, subpoena, search warrant, etc.) or other legal requirements of any governmental authority, (ii) would potentially mitigate our liability in an actual or potential lawsuit, (iii) is otherwise necessary to protect our rights or property, or (iv) is necessary to protect the legal rights or property of others.

**Security.**  Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be secure, therefore, we cannot ensure the security of any information you send to us and you do so at your own risk. If Epicor learns of a security system's breach, we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. By using this Site or providing Personal Information to us, you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues. Epicor may post a notice on this Site if a security breach occurs. If this happens, you will need a web browser or mobile device enabling you to view the Epicor Site or Application. Epicor may also send an email to you at the email address you have provided to us in these circumstances or communicate with you by other means if we can. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing.

**Links to Third-Party Sites and Co-Branded Sites.**  Epicor’s Site may contain links to third-party Sites, however, please be aware that Epicor is not responsible for and cannot control the privacy practices of these other Sites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies for these other Sites, as they may differ from ours. This Site or Epicor Product also contains links to co-branded Sites that may display Epicor's logo and trademarks but which are maintained by third parties. Such Sites may be identified by the fact that they do not display a "epicor.com" URL. Please read the privacy policy on the co-branded Site for the applicable privacy practices relating to personal information collected via that Site, as it may differ from this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Epicor on its Site.

**Special Notice to Global Visitors and Customers.**  This Site is hosted in the United States and intended for individuals outside of the European Union/European Economic Area (EU/EEA). If you are visiting from the EU/EEA, you are welcome to use the versions of the Site, which have a different Privacy Statement, intended for those regions. Because Epicor operates globally, we may transfer your Personal Information within our global operations to fulfill our obligations to you, but always subject to the limitations of applicable data protection law and this Privacy Policy. Privacy laws differ across the globe. To help visitors whose native language may not be English understand our privacy practices, we may provide special information on our Privacy Policies that may be applicable to these visitors in different languages. Epicor entities outside the United States may have supplemental privacy policies that may apply in those countries.

If you are visiting from countries with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, including those whose privacy laws may be stricter than U.S. law, please note that you are transferring your Personal Information to the United States to Epicor. By providing your Personal Information you consent to that transfer and processing.

**Marketing Communications.**  When you provide Epicor with Personal Information, we may communicate with you using the information you have given us to provide you with information we think may be of interest to you as permitted by law.

**Enforcement and More Information.**  When Epicor receives formal written complaints, it is Epicor's policy to contact the complaining user regarding their concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between Epicor and an individual.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy by Epicor.**  If in the future we change our Privacy Policy, we will post the new Privacy Policy on this Site. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy in the future. Your continued use of this Site following a change in the Privacy Policy represents consent to the new Privacy Policy to the fullest extent permitted by law. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy.

**Contacting Epicor.**  If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please email us at [webmaster@epicor.com](mailto:webmaster@epicor.com) or write to us at:

Epicor Software Corporation  
804 Las Cimas Parkway  
Austin, Texas 78746  
USA  
Attention: Legal Department
